♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
Amethyst: ♪ Amethyst
Pearl: ♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
棒!
Yeah!
停车技术不错,狮子!
Great job parking,Lion!
嘛,有点歪就是了
Eh.It's a little crooked.
当我没说,挺不错的!
Never mind.It's perfect!
把狮子停在这里真的好吗?
Is Lion gonna be okay parked out here?
哦,当然 我把他锁上就好了
Oh, yeah. Uh, I just gotta lock him up.
别担心,他不会到处跑的
Don't worry. He's not going anywhere.
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe
这是你第一次进来图书馆
this'll be your first time inside of a library.
怎么讲?
Why?
因为图书馆里都是你最喜欢的东西
Because libraries are full of your favorite thing.
都是书啊!
Books!
嘘!
Shh!
都是书啊!
Books.
好吧,是时候干掉这些书了
All right. Time to beat these books.
啊 你跟它们有什么仇?
Ah. What'd they do to you?
我是想提前准备下七年级的课程
I'm mainly trying to get a head-start on seventh grade.
我们会学很多新课程,所以
We'll be covering a lot of new stuff, so...
我想提前做好准备
I just want to be prepared.
你用手机查资料不就好了吗?
Can't you just use your phone to look stuff up?
上一次我用互联网查资料后
Last time I relied on the Internet for info,
我写出了一篇漏洞百出的,额...
I ended up writing a very, uh...
关于浣熊有热视线能力的文章
erroneous paper about raccoons having heat-vision.
浣熊有热视线?!
Raccoons have heat vision?!
嘘!
Shh!
我学习的时候你到处看看吧
You should take a look around while I get started.
这里有一堆你肯定会喜欢的东西
There's tons of stuff here I'm sure you'll love.
好滴,一会儿见
Okie. B-R-B.
纪实类?野
Nonfiction? Wild.
哇哦
Wow!
就连最下层的架子上也有很酷的书!
There's even cool books on the bottom shelves!
哈?
Huh?
你在这儿干嘛呢,小家伙?
What are you doing down here, little buddy?
没有书名!
It's blank!
哇!
Whoa!
康妮!
Connie!
看!
Look!
没有书名啊
It's blank.
这是大副巴蒂巴德威克的笔记!
It's the journal of first mate Buddy Buddwick!
-你是说,这是真货?-当然!
-Like, the real thing? -Yeah!
杰米表演过关于巴蒂的话剧
Jamie did a play about how Buddy helped
他帮助第一任市长发现了海滩市!
the first Mayor Dewey discover Beach City!
这里甚至有关于宝石建筑的画!
There's even drawings of gem locations in here!
哦,我的天!
Oh, my gosh!
别管作业了
Forget homework.
我们从头开始看吧!
Let's take it from the top!
棒!
Yeah!
在万幸躲过了死亡的命运后
After narrowly escaping certain doom,
威廉杜威船长和我,大副巴蒂
Captain William Dewey and I, his first mate Buddy,
找到了海滩市这片陆地
founded the land of Beach City.
杜威船长刻下了功勋--好吧,是铸造的--
With Captain Dewey's legacy cemented -- well, bronzed --
我在想我的功绩会是什么
I wondered what my legacy would be.
会有后人记住我的名字吗?
Would anyone remember my name?
还是会被时间的海浪冲刷的无影无踪呢?
Or will it be washed away by the ocean of time?
我把巴蒂想象成是杰米愁容满面的样子
I'm picturing buddy as Jamie being all sad.
哦,不错,他入戏的样子
Oh, yeah. Drama zone.
不!吾辈不能就这么消失!
No! I shall not disappear!
吾辈不会以大副的身份逝去!
I shan't die a lowly first mate!
吾辈会用一生达成伟业!
I schwill do something great with my life!
我将探索全球以求名留青史!
I'll comb the world in search of greatness!
从此开启了我人生的新篇章--
And so began a new chapter of my life --
即探索先前未探索之事物
to explore the previously unexplored
在世界上留下吾之印记!
and to make my mark on the world!
旅途持续了若干个日夜
I traveled for many days and nights
直到,最终,我到达了某种田地
until, finally, I found myself in a field of sorts...
倒不如说,是某种战地
or, should I say, a field of swords,
这里散布着巨大的,香甜的草莓
intermingled with giant, sweet-smelling strawberries
和人脑袋一样大
as big as one's head.
“谁能握持如此巨大的武器呢?”我细细思考
"Who could have wielded such a weapon?" I pondered.
“又有什么样的战争用到了这样的武器呢?”
"What sort of battle could this have been used for?"
我绞尽脑汁
I contemplated.
我不停地速写,沉浸在深思当中
I continued to sketch, sinking into deep concentration
突然我感到一只熟悉的手的触摸
when I suddenly felt the touch of a familiar hand.
侬好
Ahoy.
向您请安
Salutations.
原来是两只水晶战士
It was two of the Crystal Gems.
嗯
Hmm.
宝石们以前应该穿着不一样吧
Would the Gems have looked different back then?
对,肯定的
Yes. Definitely.
原来是两只宝石战士
It was two of the Crystal Gems
她们曾经从海怪那救下了船长
that had saved my captain from a sea beast.
我们现在是来救你的
And now we're here to save you.
但是我没有陷入危险啊
But I'm not in peril.
我只是个卑微的旅者,只求名字能
I'm just a humble traveler who wants my name
被后世的所有人所记住
to be remembered by everyone for all time.
这个嘛,不要在此逗留,旅者
Well, travel not here, traveler,
只因此地十分危险
as this place is very dangerous.
好吧,我去别的地方
Very well. I'll go elsewhere.
等等!
Wait!
地球上还有很多地方
There are many places on this Earth
像你这样的人类不应该造访
that a human like you should avoid.
我给你标记了这些地方以便查找
Here's a convenient marking of all the places
这些地方你绝对,任何情况下,都不能去
where you should absolutely, under no circumstances, visit
不然你短暂的生命会更短暂
if you'd like to keep your short life.
只有最勇敢,最无畏,
Only the bravest, most courageous,
最值得铭记的探险家才敢
most memorable explorers would dare
到这些美妙的地方探索
to visit these fascinating places.
对,我刚刚才说过
Yes, that's essentially what I just said.
不管怎样,还好我给你点明了
Anyway, glad we cleared that up.
再了个见!
Fare thee well!
对啊,如果我探索了这些地方
Surely,if I do explore these places,
我将会以勇敢和无畏被人铭记!
I'll be remembered as brave and courageous!
他还画了通讯中心
He drew the communication hub.
闪闪鼻涕虫?
Sparkling slugs?
他怎么想到这些名字的?
Where'd he get these names from?
哦!这个名字他猜对了!
Ooh!He got this one right!
感觉好像又去了一遍这些地方
I feel like I'm back there.
这是什么地方?
What's this place?
这个我也不知道
I don't know this one.
哦!看起来他还去了宝宝基地!
Ooh! It looks like he went to the kindergarten!
我发现自己身处一个最令人惊讶的地方
I found myself at the most amazing locations.
嗯嗯,很尖
Hmm.Very pointy.
但是我还是隐约有种感觉
Though I could not shake the feeling
感觉这次旅行有什么...不对劲
that something about this journey felt a bit...off.
嗯
Hmm.
我很好奇为什么这些小洞会在这儿
I wonder why all these tiny caves are here.
-嘿,伙计!
-Hey, Buddy!
对-对就是我
Th-This is Buddy speaking.
从我的洞里出来
Get out of my hole.
嗟乎,原来是第三只水晶战士
Lo, it was the third Crystal Gem.
你是,呃,住在这里?
Do you, uh, live here?
以前是!
Used to!
现在我就是不时回来
Nowadays, I just come back every so often
看看家人怎么样了
to see how the fam's doing.
家人?
The fam?
嘿,最近怎样啊?
Hey, how you been?
嗷!你是不是长高了?
Aw!You getting taller?
呃,等我一下,有个客人来了
Uh, give me a sec --I have a visitor.
你来这儿干啥?!
Why are you here?!
哦,我的错 来,我给你看看
Oh. My apologies. Here, I'll show you.
我现在是作为探险家在进行环球探险
I've been traveling the globe as an adventurer and explorer.
赞!
Neat!
我一直在旅途中
I've been on a journey to discover
探索无人曾到达的地方
places no one has ever been before.
但是看这个地方的样子
But by the looks of this place,
很多人已经来过这里了
many people have been here before.
等下,这张地图是你自己做的?
Hold on. Did you make this map?
是你的同僚帮我标记的
It was drawn up for me by your compatriots.
就是说,噗
So, pbht!
你又独立发现了什么呢?
What have you discovered on it?
这个嘛,我...发现了...
Well, I uh..That is...
哦,呃 哦 天啊
Oh. Uh...Oh, dear.
这张图上没有一处是我自己发现的!
I haven't discovered a single thing on this map!
就是说啊,哥们
Yeah, man.
你只是在跟着别人的足迹旅行罢了
You're just following someone else's footsteps.
原来这就是我
And here I was,
自诩为伟大的冒险家和探索者
claiming to be a great explorer and adventurer,
但自己其实只是...
when all I really am...
只是个游客!
is a tourist!
哇 别当着我面儿伤心啊
Whoa.Don't get all sad on me.
怪不得我感觉有什么不对劲!
This is why my journey hasn't felt right!
额
Uh...
呃,哦,对了!
Uh, oh, yeah!
你为什么不去试试找沙城堡呢?
Why don't you try and find the sand castle?
呃,啥?
Uh, wha?
一边去,我给你指下
Out of the way. I'll show you.
它就在这片全都是沙的地方
It's right around here in this sandy area.
-真的?-当然!
-Really? -Yeah!
人说它永远不会停在一个地方
They say it's never in the same place twice.
它总是在沙漠各地不断重建
It's always rebuilding itself all over the desert.
听起来是个再合适不过的探险了!
That sounds like the perfect adventure for me!
我还将会是第一个看到它的人!
And I'll be the first one to see it!
呵 好吧
Heh. Okay.
谢谢你的帮助 再见!
Thank you for your help. Goodbye!
欢迎随时回来!
Come back anytime!
但也别太频繁!
But not too much!
我已经在这片沙漠中漫步了10天了
I've been wandering this desert for 10 days now.
我想我该脱下探险家之大衣
I suppose I could take off my explorer's coat
好歹能凉快一会
for a bit of relief,
但是如果我不穿大衣的话,人们看到我就会想
but if I wasn't wearing this, people would see me and think,
"哦,就是个普通人到处走而已
"Oh, just some man wandering around.
一点都不重要
Not important at all.
可不是嘛,他连神秘的沙城堡都找不到!"
Why, he can't even find the elusive sand castle!"
“哈哈哈”他们会这么笑
"Ha, ha, ha" they'd say.
“真是个傻瓜”他们会这么说
“What a fool," they'd continue.
呃
Ugh.
这就是了---这就是我冒险旅途的尽头
This is it, then -- the end of my adventure.
我跟着一张地图来到了我的终结之地
I've just followed a map to my own end.
这就是我逝去前所能看到的最后一幕--
And this will be the last thing I ever see as I expire --
一个天使和她的--一、二、三--
an angel and her -- one, two, three --
好几只狮子,来取走我的灵魂
several lions, here for my soul.
这就完结了吗?
Is this the end?
我猜是的
I guess so.
哦等下,后面还有一堆呢!
Oh, wait. There's a bunch more.
我慢慢恢复了意识
As I slowly regained consciousness,
我看到了一个高大的人影
I became aware of a large figure
是个巨大的女人
in the shape of a giant woman.
她卷曲的秀发
The ringlets of her hair
铺满了她的肩和背
spilled over her shoulders and back
就像一丛玫瑰
like a swath of roses.
妈妈!
Mom!
嘿 你还好吗?
Hey. Are you okay?
我意识到自己被包围在她的...
I realized I was surrounded by her pack of...
七只狮子?
Seven lions?!
求求你--别吃我!
Please -- don't eat me!
哦,别担心 我们没有恶意
Oh, don't worry. We mean no harm.
那就好
That's good.
呃
Ugh.
你们人类为什么要来这种地方?
What brings a human out to a place like this?
我以前是船上的大副,但是我们已经找到了陆地
I was a first mate on a ship, but we found land.
然后我意识到自己并不想呆在那片陆地
And then I realized I didn't want to stay in that land,
所以我就去找其他陆地
so I went to find more land.
然后有人说不要去找那片陆地
But then I was told not to find that land
因为太危险了
because it was really dangerous.
但是我想证明自己所以...
But I wanted to prove myself and...
这样,我把全部都写在这儿了
Look. I wrote it all down here.
为什么我要费劲去找沙城堡
Why am I looking for the sand castle
它甚至可能根本就不存在!
that probably doesn't even exist?
-沙城堡?-对啊
-A sand castle? -Yes.
我已经在沙漠中搜寻了数周
I've combed these deserts for weeks,
根本连影子都没看到
and there's been no sign of one.
那个不就是吗?
Would that be a sign of one?
那就是了!我一定要记录下来!That's it! I've gotta record this!
我一定要--等下
I've got to -- Wait.
你先看见的 所以根本就不算数!
You saw it first. This doesn't count at all!
我真是个糟糕的探索者
I'm a terrible explorer.
吃了我吧 我就这点用处了
Eat me. It's all I'm good for.
等等,等等,你说的不对
Now, now, that's not true at all.
当然,这些地方确实有前人探索过
Sure, all these places have been explored before,
但是从未有人以如此亲切的语言记载过
but they haven't been recorded so intimately
像这笔记里那样
as they have been in this journal.
你的记载使得这些地方又变得新鲜和特殊
It makes them new and special all over again
所有读者都会有同感
for any reader to experience.
你有没有想过当个作家?
Have you ever considered becoming an author?
这样我就成为了一名作家
And become an author I did.
我指如疾风,写出了一本又一本书
I wrote up a storm, making book after book,
我意识到如此多的书,可以填满一座图书馆!
so many until I realized I could fill a library with them!
我知道了!
I get it!
就是巴蒂巴德威克图书馆!
The Buddy Buddwick Library!
嘘!
Shh!
他确实在这镇上留下了印记
He really did leave a mark on this town.
哇 等一下
Whoa. Hold the phone.
他就长那个样子吗?
Is that what he looked like?
我们的想象错到家了
We imagined him way off.
我还是喜欢我们的版本
I kind of liked our version better.
我也是
Me, too.